GAURAV ADANI

CHARTERED ACCOUNTANT

Mumbai, Maharashtra • +91 9096860469 • gauravadn123@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A chartered accountant with almost 2.5 years of experience in financial planning, budgeting, variance analysis, reducing costs and increasing efficiency. I have gained immense experience in supply chain function as a part of the biggest ecommerce organization in the country and in banking sector.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Finance Analyst, Flipkart Pvt India Ltd

Feb 2024 - Present

- Part of team handling multi million-dollar project of building various fulfilment and sortation centers of Flipkart.
- Collaborating with cross-functional stakeholders, analyzing ROI of various automation projects and making rational decisions on implementation and spends looking after financial as well as non-financial factors.
- Looking over 40-45+ Flipkart warehouses across India, analyzing their budget requirements, trying to optimize budgets. Together with all the teams, have led to savings of around **5000 lakhs** in FY 2024
- Involved in implementations of various automation initiatives which has led to major savings in operating expenses as well improvement in speed and delivery.
- One of the highlights would be to drive the budgeting of one of the biggest upcoming warehouses in the country.
- Preparation of Annual Operating Plans, presenting data to CFO.

Manager, ICICI Bank

Nov 2022 - Feb 2024

- Part of Bank Cards team
- Preparation of quarterly as well as annual budgets, forecasting financial results, variance analysis and preparing investor presentations
- · Engaging in bank level competitive analysis and looking out for ways to avoid revenue leakage for the bank
- Various Ad-hoc analysis such as evaluating prospective banking products, their long term profitability for the bank

EDUCATION

Chartered Accountant

Mar 2018 - May 2022

The Institute of Chartered Accountants Of India

• CA Final-465/800

Bachelor of Commerce

Apr 2019 - Mar 2021

Mumbai University

• GPA: CGPI 8.24/10.00

SKILLS

• Stakeholder Management, Fast Learner, Variance Analysis and Microsoft Office Proficiency.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Cleared all levels of CA in 1st attempt and was a merit holder in Class 10 and Class 12.
- Awarded the '2nd prize' in 'English' language in IGCSE level in school.
- Cost optimization to the tune of **500 Crores** during the FY 2024 in Flipkart.